{"data":[{"question":"Although the scientific community had hoped that the field of transplantation ________, the shortage of organ donors has curtailed research.","a":"progress","b":"had progressed","c":"would progress","d":"progressing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use the future in the past form\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The seed heads of teasel plants raise the nap on coarse tweed cloth ________ than do the machine tools invented to replace them.","a":"more efficiently","b":"efficiently more","c":"efficient","d":"most efficient","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Comparative of adj\/adv:\u00a0\n+ Short adj\/adv: adj\/adv + er + than.\u00a0\n+ Long adj: More + adj\/adv + than.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"We are all amenable ________ discipline.","a":"with","b":"at","c":"to","d":"for","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To be amenable to.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"________ unknown quantities is the task of algebra.","a":"To found","b":"Find","c":"The find","d":"Finding","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Both gerund and infinitive can be subject: \n+ Gerund: are often used when actions are real, concrete or completed.\u00a0\n+ Infinitive: are often used when actions are unreal, abstract, or future.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"I read two books but neither book ________ very interesting.","a":"has been","b":"had been","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The subject (Neither book) is singular","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The yearly path of the sun around the heavens ________.","a":"is known as the ecliptic","b":"known as the ecliptic","c":"it is known to be ecliptic","d":"knowing as the ecliptic","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To be known as something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"This table is already ________.","a":"occupy","b":"occupied","c":"occupation","d":"occupational","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Passive voice of simple present: Be + PP.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"A dolphin ________ a porpoise in that it has a longer nose.","a":"different","b":"differs","c":"different than","d":"differs from","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Differ from: to be different from something in some way.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The ________ I'm late is that I missed the bus.","a":"reason","b":"reasoned","c":"reasonable","d":"reasonably","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The + Noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"________ like \"Macdonalds\" and \"Kentucky fried chicken\" have used franchising to extend their sales internationally.","a":"Chain's restaurants","b":"Chains restaurants","c":"Chain restaurant","d":"Chain restaurants","answer":"4","explain":"- Chains restaurants is plural","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"}]}